Right.
So in this first section we've been learning about the basics of this environment.
We've been learning about Sublime Text Editor.
We've learned about the basics of HTML, how it really is like a little skeleton that helps you build
up your website.
We use source code that is made up of what are these things called tags?
That's it.
They're called tags.
And every tag has a opening and a closing.
You can see the difference because it's got a little forward slash to show you the closing.
We've looked at how you have a HTML opener and closer.
Then you have your header section, which is this part which you don't really need to do much about
besides maybe putting a title.
If you want to indicate your title, then you have your body section that is between body and close
body.
But now it's your turn to have a bit of a try.
So you remember.
You always save when you go across and have a look.
It's your turn to try.
So this is what we would like you to do.
What I would like you to do is let's put this as H2 It is.
What?
What do you think?
If you can actually think the.
What should we choose?
Oh la la.
Okay, there's a great.
Who the heck knows what that tag is?
What do you think the tag does, right?
So what I would like you to do and just, you know, I think this is a great little thing because when
you see the tag and you try to figure it out and it's quite cool, we're not going to tell you it's
time for you to learn by trying for yourself.
So what I want you to do is very simple, very simple.
It's the tag you want to find out what it does.
So you've heard of Google?
Excellent.
What we'd like you to do I'm not going to do it is what is the tag HTML okay I want you to go and Google
it.
Read about it so you can get a bit of an understanding because there's some fun things that you can
do with it that you might not understand if you just do it straight away.
And then once you've done that, give it a try.
We'd like you to add an Li Ally tag to your website.
So?
Got it.
What do you think the tag does?
Go to Google.
Do a little Google search of it.
See what it comes up with.
Read that so that you are being active in your learning.
And then when you've done that go aha.
Go back and put it in.
Try an ally tag but read it first so you can see what it does.
So you can see how you can change it from a straightforward ally tag by doing a little something to
make it into something slightly different.
But you're going to have to go and find that out for yourself.
So that's your task for this first thing, to let you play a little bit, get used to the environment
and put in some H1, some H2, some bolds if you like, and play a little bit with the tag as well.
So go have fun, go learn, make mistakes.
But that's how you're going to learn.
And we're here if you've got any questions.
If you don't understand anything, feel free to pop a comment in the comment section and we will do
our best to help you.
So go out and have some fun.
Do the learning journey.